<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MIAJ TECH</title>
    <link>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MIAJ TECH</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022–2025, MIAJ Tech and the Team.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Docker</title>
      <link>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/docker/docker1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/docker/docker1/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Docker: The Ultimate Toolbox for Developers Table of Contents  What is Docker and Why Should You Care? How Does Docker Work? The Benefits of Using Docker  Consistency Across Environments Easier Collaboration Scalability Made Simple   How to Get Started with Docker  Installing Docker Creating Your First Container Exploring Docker Hub   Common Misconceptions About Docker Conclusion  What is Docker and Why Should You Care? Imagine trying to build a house without the right tools.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/kubernetes/kube1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/kubernetes/kube1/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Unleashing the Power of Kubernetes: Your Guide to Container Orchestration Magic Table of Contents  What is Kubernetes, Anyway? Why Use Kubernetes? Key Features of Kubernetes  Self-Healing Capabilities Load Balancing Scalability   How Does Kubernetes Work?  Pods Nodes Clusters   Getting Started with Kubernetes The Future of Kubernetes Conclusion: Embrace the Kubernetes Revolution  What is Kubernetes, Anyway? Managing modern applications can feel like juggling ten balls simultaneously.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux</title>
      <link>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/linux/linux1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/linux/linux1/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Discovering Linux: Your Gateway to a Smarter Computing World Table of Contents  What is Linux and Why Should You Care? The Power of Open Source Why Choose Linux for Your Computer?  Speed and Performance Security at Its Best Customizability Free to Use   An Easy Start with Linux Community Support: The Heart of Linux Conclusion: Embrace the Linux Revolution  What is Linux and Why Should You Care?
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proxmox1</title>
      <link>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/virtualization/proxmox1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/virtualization/proxmox1/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Overview Virtualization is a technology that enables the creation of IT services using resources traditionally tied to physical hardware. By distributing a physical machine&#39;s capabilities across multiple users or environments, virtualization helps to maximize its utilization.
Table of Contents  Overview Practical Example Server Usage A Brief History of Virtualization How Virtualization Works Types of Virtualization  Data Virtualization Desktop Virtualization Server Virtualization Operating System Virtualization Network Functions Virtualization (NFV)    Practical Example Imagine you have three physical servers, each with a dedicated purpose: one for email, one for web hosting, and one for running internal legacy applications.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proxmox3</title>
      <link>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/virtualization/proxmox3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/virtualization/proxmox3/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Discover What&#39;s New in Proxmox 8.2: Features and Download Information Explore the exciting new features of Proxmox 8.2, including enhancements in automated installations, Cloudinit templates, backups, storage, and networking.
Table of Contents  Automated and Unattended Installations VMware ESX VM Import Wizard nftables Firewall LXC Device Passthrough Advanced Backup Settings Extended ACME-Enabled CAs User Interface Enhancements Core Technology Updates  Proxmox 8.2 New Features Automated and Unattended Installations Streamline your setup process with new automated and unattended installation options.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Hugo page bundles folder</title>
      <link>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/post/bundle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/post/bundle/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Page bundles are an optional way to organize page resources within Hugo. You can opt-in to using page bundles in Hugo Clarity with `usePageBundles` in your site configuration --- or in a page&#39;s front matter.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proxmox2</title>
      <link>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/virtualization/proxmox2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hafizahmadjamil.github.io/hugo.github.io/virtualization/proxmox2/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Discover What&#39;s New in Proxmox 8.2: Features and Download Information Explore the exciting new features of Proxmox 8.2, including enhancements in automated installations, Cloudinit templates, backups, storage, and networking.
Table of Contents  Automated and Unattended Installations VMware ESX VM Import Wizard nftables Firewall LXC Device Passthrough Advanced Backup Settings Extended ACME-Enabled CAs User Interface Enhancements Core Technology Updates  Proxmox 8.2 New Features Automated and Unattended Installations Streamline your setup process with new automated and unattended installation options.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
